codemyconcept.com 2019-01-24

# CodeMyConcept: the best PSD to HTML service on the planet! | convert PSD2HTML

Please review our Privacy Policy, which is part of our [Terms of Service](https://www.codemyconcept.com/terms-of-services). This Privacy Policy describes your privacy rights regarding our collection, use, storage, sharing, and protection of your information. By browsing this website and using its services (the “Services”) you agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy. 

We control the ways your personal information is collected and processed:  
P2H Inc. dba CodeMyConcept Corp.  
7848 W Sahara Ave, Las Vegas, NV 89117, USA

### Information Collected

CodeMyConcept will require you to provide some information in order to provide our Services to you. This is an example of the type of information we will require from you to be collected or submitted to CodeMyConcept through our order form, product request, and other pages. You will most likely be asked to share the following information: 

  * Personal information including email address, name, contact details etc.;
  * Order-specific information, including source files and project notes;
  * Some specific details of Client’s project in general.

### How We Use Your Information

The information you share with CodeMyConcept including your personal information is used to complete your order. Personal information means information that relates to you and allows us to identify you, either directly or indirectly. For example, your email address is used for notifications about the status of your order and communications with you.

Also we may use your personal information in order to provide you with our newsletters and marketing information with news and special offers from CodeMyConcept. Your have a right to opt-out in each email we send to you or by emailing us to [ support@codemyconcept.com](mailto:support@codemyconcept.com).

We do not sell or trade any information you shared with us.  
We do not collect and store any sensitive information about you and any information from children under 16 years old.  
All the information provided to CodeMyConcept online will remain safe and secure at all times.

### Retention of Information

We store your information in the United States and Europe. We will retain your information only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. 

We will retain and use your information to the extent necessary for accounting and reporting purposes, fraud screening, disputes resolving, enforcing our legal agreements and policies and to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your information to comply with applicable laws).

### How We Share and Transfer Your Information

To provide you with the Services your information (including personal information) may be transferred outside the United States to Europe and may be processed by our exclusive contractors and subcontractors.

It also may be shared with our lawyers, accountants, auditors and other professional advisers, court or other government body as required by law (but only that portion of your information which is legally required to be disclosed).

We take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your information is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer or sharing of your information will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your information.

By submitting such information you represent that you agree to that transfer and sharing.

### Your Data Protection Rights

With respect to your personal information you have the following rights:

  * the right to access, update or to delete the information we have on you.
  * the right of rectification. You have the right to have your information rectified if it is inaccurate or incomplete.
  * the right to object. You have the right to object to our processing of your personal information.
  * the right of restriction. You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal information.
  * the right to data portability. You have the right to receive your personal information, provided to us, in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format and have the right to transmit those information to another company without hindrance from CodeMyConcept (where it’s feasible).
  * the right to withdraw consent. You also have the right to withdraw your consent to your personal information processing at any time.

To exercise any of these rights please contact us through [Client Area](https://www.codemyconcept.com/client) or by emailing to [ data.protection@codemyconcept.com](mailto:data.protection@codemyconcept.com). Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests.

### Information Security

This website uses state-of-the-art digital encryption and security technologies to protect the privacy and security of our clients’ information, we work with specific security measures to ensure protection and prevent the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

All data passing from your computer to us is authenticated and encrypted. Any information sent from your computer to us is carefully handled and protected at all times.

### Why We Use Cookies

Cookies are small pieces of text sent by your web browser by a website you visit. A cookie file is stored in your web browser and allows us to recognize you and make your next visit easier and this website more useful to you.

Our cookies serve various purposes, but are generally either necessary or essential to the functioning of this website and its Services.

Strictly Necessary or Essential cookies:

these cookies let you move around the website and use its essential features. Without these technologies, some services you have asked for cannot be provided.   
Please note that these technologies do not gather any information about you that could be used for marketing or remembering where you've been on the Internet. 

Performance cookies:

these cookies collect information about how you use our website e.g. which pages you visit, and if you experience any errors.  
These cookies do not collect any information that could identify you and are only used to help us improve how our website works, understand what interests our users and measure how effective our content is by providing anonymous statistics and data regarding how our website is used. 

Functionality cookies: 

these cookies are used to provide services or to remember settings to improve your visit.  
If you do not wish to receive cookies or store them on your computer any more please change your browsing settings and/or delete all received cookies before. If you do this, however, you may have to manually adjust some preferences every time you visit a website and some services and functionalities may not work.

### Links to Other Websites

This website may contain links to third-party websites, which are not owned and operated by CodeMyConcept. Any information you provide to those websites will be governed by their own policies. CodeMyConcept assumes no responsibility or liability for any policies of such independent websites.

### Updates to Privacy Policy

Your privacy is very important to us and we may update this Privacy Policy from time to time, to ensure that the information we provide to you is up to date and in accordance with the relevant data protection laws. Any updates of this Policy will be published on this website.

### Contact Us

Questions, comments and requests regarding this Privacy Policy should be addressed to [ data.protection@codemyconcept.com](mailto:data.protection@codemyconcept.com) .
